Finding Aid for University of Michigan Class Albums
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 1871 Class Album (Literary and Engineering)
  - Students
    - Goodell, Henry M. (Box 16)
    - Gorton, Charles E. (Box 16)
    - Granger, Henry C. (Box 16)
    - Green, Samuel S. (Box 16)
    - Hamilton, Alexander W. (Box 16)
    - Harsha, Walter S. (Box 16)
    - Hudson, Richard (Box 16)
    - Hudson, Preston (Box 16)
    - Hutchins, Harry B. (Box 16)
    - Knight, Earle J. (Box 16)
    - Latson, Morton W. (Box 16)
    - Latham, Charles K. (Box 16)
    - Littlefield, Josiah L. (Box 16)
    - Mark, Edward L. (Box 16)
    - Mason, Lyman (Box 16)
    - Mercer, Joseph A. (Box 16)
    - Merrill, William (Box 16)
    - Millerd, W. Birchard (Box 16)
    - Montrose, Henry W. (Box 16)
    - Otis, Arthur C. (Box 16)
    - Pennington, Baron H. (Box 16)
    - Parshall, Adrian J. (Box 16)
    - Perry, Elliott D. (Box 16)
    - Philipps, Horace (Box 16)
    - Phinney, Rufus F. (Box 16)
    - Pratt, Charles (Box 16)
    - Preston, Benjamin T. (Box 16)
    - Randall, Perry A. (Box 16)
    - Raymond, Alexander B. (Box 16)
    - Remick, Frank (Box 16)
    - Rice, Benjamin E. (Box 16)
    - Ritter, William F. (Box 16)
    - Rust, Charles A. (Box 16)
    - Seavy, Gideon W. (Box 16)
    - Sleeper, John W. (Box 16)
    - Smith, Curtis C. (Box 16)
    - Sumner, Edward B. (Box 16)
    - Walker, Samuel W. (Box 16)
    - Warden, James A. (Box 16)
    - Webb, L. Burkitt (Box 16)
    - Wilkinson, Charles M. (Box 16)
    - Wilson, Floyd B. (Box 16)
    - Willett, Charles J. (Box 16)
    - Wright, Robert M. (Box 16)
- 1872 Class
  - Miscellaneous
    - Class Banner (Box 17)
  - Faculty
    - President Angell (Box 17)
    - Dr. Williams (Box 17)
    - Dr. Douglas (Box 17)
    - Prof. Winchell (Box 17)
    - Dr. Ford (Box 17)
    - Prof. Frieze (Box 17)
    - Judge Campbell (Box 17)
    - Prof. Wood (Box 17)
    - Judge Walker (Box 17)
    - Judge Cooley (Box 17)
    - Andrew Ten Brook (Librarian) (Box 17)
    - Prof. Olney (Box 17)
    - Prof. Adams (Box 17)
    - Prof. Tyler (Box 17)
    - Prof. Kent (law) (Box 17)
    - Prof. Cocker (Box 17)
    - Prof. D'Ioge (Box 17)
    - Prof. Morris (Box 17)
    - Prof. Merriman (Box 17)
    - Prof. James (Box 17)
    - Prof. Pattengill (Box 17)
    - Prof. Walter (Box 17)
    - Ex. President Tappan (Box 17)
    - Ex. President Haven (Box 17)
  - Students
    - F.D. Andrus, B.A. (Box 17)
    - E.J. Ayer, B.A. (Box 17)
    - C.O. Baker, B.A. (Box 17)
    - A. Barber, B.A. (Box 17)
    - C.G. Bennett, B.A. (Box 17)
    - S.H. Betheal, B.S. (Box 17)
    - Prof. Evans. (Box 17)
    - Prof. Spence (Box 17)
    - W.A. Brooks, B.A. (Box 17)
    - A.H. Brown, B.W. (Box 17)
    - R.E. Brinker, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.M. Burgett, PhB. (Box 17)
    - J. Christie, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H.F. Burton, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H.N. Chute, B.S. (Box 17)
    - C.Clark, B.A. (Box 17)
    - G. Colt, Jr., B.A. (Box 17)
    - G.E. Cochran, B.A. (Box 17)
    - E.A. Cooley, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H. Dey, Ph.B. (Box 17)
    - C. Donovan, C.E. (Box 17)
    - J.F. Dutton, B.A. (Box 17)
    - F.L. Geddes, B.A. (Box 17)
    - W.J. Herdman, Ph.B. (Box 17)
    - J.H. Flagg, C.E. (Box 17)
    - R. Foster, B.S. (Box 17)
    - E.L. Hill, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H. Hiestand, B.S. (Box 17)
    - J. Hillegass, B.A. (Box 17)
    - W.H. Hinman, B.S. (Box 17)
    - W.A. Hosmer, B.S. (Box 17)
    - C.L. Houseman, Ph.B. (Box 17)
    - G.F. Hurd, B.A. (Box 17)
    - L.M. Iddings, PhB. (Box 17)
    - L. H. Jennings, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.C. Jones, B.A. (Box 17)
    - C. Jones, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H.M. Keeler, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.H. Kirkpatrick, B.A. (Box 17)
    - I.J. Klotz, C.E. (Box 17)
    - W.R. Leigh, B.A. (Box 17)
    - C.B. Lothrop, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H.H. Lyons, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J. H Maguire, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.J. Mapel, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J. MacMagrath, B.A. (Box 17)
    - W.H. McKee, B.A. (Box 17)
    - L.McLean, B.S. (Box 17)
    - S. G. Milner, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.A. Mitchell, C.E. (Box 17)
    - A. Moffat, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J. Morrow, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.W. Morton, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H. Neuhoff, B.A. (Box 17)
    - E.W. Pendleton, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.W. Phelps, Ph.B. (Box 17)
    - L. Parsons (Box 17)
    - H. Reed, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.B. Rosevelt, B.S. (Box 17)
    - D.C. Rexford, B.A. (Box 17)
    - F.T. Seeley, B.S. (Box 17)
    - E.W. Schreeb, B.A. (Box 17)
    - M.B. Snyder, B.A. (Box 17)
    - E. M. Spaulding, C.E. (Box 17)
    - B. Smith, B.S. (Box 17)
    - H.B. Swartz, B.A. (Box 17)
    - M.F. Temple, C.E. (Box 17)
    - F.H. Tabor, B.A. (Box 17)
    - R.F. Tinkham, B.A. (Box 17)
    - M. Tschirgi, C.E. (Box 17)
    - C. K. Turner, B.A. (Box 17)
    - W.T. Underwood, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H. D. Updike, B.A. (Box 17)
    - H. Van Vranken, B.A. (Box 17)
    - G.P. Voorheis, B.A. (Box 17)
    - T.B. Willson, B.A. (Box 17)
    - R. Woodhhams, B.A. (Box 17)
    - J.A. Woods, B.A. (Box 17)
    - R.S. Woodward, C.E. (Box 17)
    - C.C. Worthington, B.S. (Box 17)
    - J.B. Armstrong (Box 17)
    - R.C. Davis (Asst. libr.) (Box 17)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - Robert ? (Box 17)
    - Jimmie ? (Box 17)
    - Class Group (Box 17)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon Seniors (Box 17)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon Society. Omicron chapter. (Box 17)
    - Law Building. (Box 17)
    - Medical Building. (Box 17)
    - Laboratory. (Box 17)
    - Observatory. (Box 17)
    - "Franklin" statue presented by '70 (Box 17)
    - Ruth (gleaning) (Box 17)
    - Nydia (Box 17)
    - General view of campus (Box 17)
    - Walk to Laboratory (Box 17)
    - Walk to south college (Box 17)
    - Main entrance to campus (Box 17)
    - Main Street. (Box 17)
    - Huron St. (Box 17)
    - Library and Reading room (?) (Box 17)
    - Literary Adelphi Hall (Box 17)
    - Alpha Nu Hall (Box 17)
    - University Hall (Box 17)
    - View in Museum. (Box 17)
    - View in Museum. (Apollo Belvidere) (Box 17)
      [131]
    - View in Museum. (Box 17)
- 1872 Class Album
  - Buildings
    - University Hall, viewed from the West (Box 18)
    - General View of Campus, from Southwest (Box 18)
    - Law College, from the West (Box 18)
    - Medical College, from the North (Box 18)
    - Observatory, from Northwest (Box 18)
    - Chemical Laboratory, from the Northwest (Box 18)
    - Alpha Nu Hall (Box 18)
  - Faculty
    - Adams, C. K. (Box 18)
    - Angell, James B. (Box 18)
    - Cocker, B. F. (Box 18)
    - D'Ooge, M. L. (Box 18)
    - Douglas, S. H. (Box 18)
    - Ford, C. L. (Box 18)
    - Frieze, H. S. (Box 18)
    - Haven, E. O. (Box 18)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 18)
    - Merriman, Geo. B. (Box 18)
    - Morris, Geo. S. (Box 18)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 18)
    - Tappan (Box 18)
    - Tyler, M. C. (Box 18)
    - Walter, Edward L. (Box 18)
    - Williams, Geo. P. (Box 18)
    - Winchell, Alex (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Nydia (Box 18)
    - Ruth Gleaning, by Randolph Rogers (Box 18)
    - Class Banner (Box 18)
  - Students
    - Allyn, Geo W. (Box 18)
    - Andrus, Frank D. (Box 18)
    - Ayer, Edwin I. (Box 18)
    - Baker, Chas O. (Box 18)
    - Barber, Austin (Box 18)
    - Bennett, Chas G. (Box 18)
    - Bethea, Solomon H. (Box 18)
    - Brooks, Walter A. (Box 18)
    - Brown, Archer H. (Box 18)
    - Bunker, Robert E. (Box 18)
    - Burgett, J. M. H. (Box 18)
    - Burton, Henry F. (Box 18)
    - Christie, James (Box 18)
    - Chute, Horatio N. (Box 18)
    - Clark, Charlemagne (Box 18)
    - Cochran, Geo.E. (Box 18)
    - Colt, Geo.(Jr.) (Box 18)
    - Cooley, Edgar A. (Box 18)
    - Dey, Hamilton (Box 18)
    - Dickson, Geo (Box 18)
    - Donovan, Cornelius (Box 18)
    - Dutton, John F. (Box 18)
    - Flagg, John H. (Box 18)
    - Foster, Riley (Box 18)
    - Geddes, Fred L. (Box 18)
    - Haskell, William S. (Box 18)
    - Herdman, Will J. (Box 18)
    - Hiestand, Henry (Box 18)
    - Hill, Eben L. (Box 18)
    - Hillegass, Jeremiah (Box 18)
    - Hinman, William H. (Box 18)
    - Hosmer, Warren A. (Box 18)
    - Houseman, Chas L. (Box 18)
    - Hurd, Geo F. (Box 18)
    - Iddings, Louis M. (Box 18)
    - Jennings, Louis H. (Box 18)
    - Jones, Clark (Box 18)
    - Jones, Jos C. (Box 18)
    - Keeler, Hiram M. (Box 18)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jas H. (Box 18)
    - Klotz, Otto J. (Box 18)
    - Leigh, William R. (Box 18)
    - Lothrop, Chas B. (Box 18)
    - Lyons, Herbert H. (Box 18)
    - Maguire, Jas H. (Box 18)
    - Mapel, John J. (Box 18)
    - McGrath, Jos (Box 18)
    - McLean, Lester M. (Box 18)
    - McRee, William H. (Box 18)
    - Milner, Samuel G. (Box 18)
    - Mitchell, John A. (Box 18)
    - Moffat, Addison (Box 18)
    - Morrow, Jackson (Box 18)
    - Morton, John W. (Box 18)
    - Myers, Hiram (Box 18)
    - Neuhoff, Hector (Box 18)
    - Orr, David L. (Box 18)
    - Parsons, Lewis B. (Box 18)
    - Pendleton, Edward W. (Box 18)
    - Phelps, John W. (Box 18)
    - Reed, Homer (Box 18)
    - Rexford, Dwight C. (Box 18)
    - Rosevelt, John B. (Box 18)
    - Schreeb, Ernest (Box 18)
    - Seeley, Frank L. (Box 18)
    - Smith, Barton (Box 18)
    - Snyder, Monroe B. (Box 18)
    - Spaulding, Edmund M. (Box 18)
    - Swartz, Hiram B. (Box 18)
    - Tabor, Frank H. (Box 18)
    - Temple, Marvin F. (Box 18)
    - Tinkham, Russell F. (Box 18)
    - Tschirgi, Matthew (Box 18)
    - Turner, Chas K. (Box 18)
    - Underwood, William T. (Box 18)
    - Updike, Herbert D. (Box 18)
    - Van Vranken, Howard H. (Box 18)
    - Voorheis, Geo. P. (Box 18)
    - Wilson, Theodore B. (Box 18)
    - Woodhams, Roland (Box 18)
    - Woods, James A. (Box 18)
    - Woodward, Robert S. (Box 18)
    - Worthington, Chas L. (Box 18)
- 1872 Class Album
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - Class Banner (Box 19)
    - University Hall (Box 19)
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Charles K. (Box 19)
    - Angell, James B. (Box 19)
    - Campbell, James (Box 19)
    - Cocker, Benjamin (Box 19)
    - Cooley, Thomas (Box 19)
    - D'Ooge, M. L. (Box 19)
    - Douglas, S. H. (Box 19)
    - Ford, C. L. (Box 19)
    - Frieze, H. S. (Box 19)
    - Haven, E. O. (Box 19)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 19)
    - Kent, Charles A. (Box 19)
    - Merriman, Geo. B. (Box 19)
    - Morris, Geo. S. (Box 19)
    - Olney, E. (Box 19)
    - Pattengill, A. H. (Box 19)
    - Spence, A. K. (Box 19)
    - Tappan, Henry P. (Box 19)
    - Ten Brook, Andrew (Box 19)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 19)
    - Walker, George (Box 19)
    - Walter, Edward L. (Box 19)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 19)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 19)
  - Students
    - Allyn, George W. (Box 19)
    - Andrus, Frank D. (Box 19)
    - Ayer, Edwin J. (Box 19)
    - Baker, Chas O. (Box 19)
    - Barber, Austin (Box 19)
    - Bennett, Chas G. (Box 19)
    - Bethea, Solomon (Box 19)
    - Brooks, Walter A. (Box 19)
    - Brown, T. A. H. (Box 19)
    - Bunker, Robert Emmet (Box 19)
    - Burgett, J. M. H. (Box 19)
    - Burton, Henry F. (Box 19)
    - Chochran, Geo. E. (Box 19)
    - Christie, Jas (Box 19)
    - Chute, H. N. (Box 19)
    - Clark, Charlemagne (Box 19)
    - Colt Jr., Geo. (Box 19)
    - Cooley, E. A. (Box 19)
    - Dey, Hamilton (Box 19)
    - Dixon (Box 19)
    - Donovan, C. (Box 19)
    - Dutton, J. Frederick (Box 19)
    - Flagg, John H. (Box 19)
    - Foster, Riley (Box 19)
    - Geddes, F. L. (Box 19)
    - Haskell, W. S. (Box 19)
    - Herdman, Will J. (Box 19)
    - Hiestand, Henry (Box 19)
    - Hill, E. L. (Box 19)
    - Hillegass, Jerry (Box 19)
    - Hinman, W. H. (Box 19)
    - Hosmer, W. A. (Box 19)
    - Houseman, C. L. (Box 19)
    - Hurd, G. F. (Box 19)
    - Iddings, Lewis M. (Box 19)
    - Jennings, L. H. (Box 19)
    - Jones, C. (Box 19)
    - Jones, J. C. (Box 19)
    - Keeler, H. M. (Box 19)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jas H. (Box 19)
    - Klotz, Otto Julius (Box 19)
    - Leigh, William R. (Box 19)
    - Lothrop, Charles B. (Box 19)
    - Lyons, H. Hess (Box 19)
    - Maguire, Herbert (Box 19)
    - Mapel, J. J. (Box 19)
    - McGrath, J. (Box 19)
    - McKee, William H. (Box 19)
    - McLean, L. M. (Box 19)
    - Milner, S. G. (Box 19)
    - Mitchell, John A. (Box 19)
    - Moffat, A. (Box 19)
    - Morrow, Jackson (Box 19)
    - Morton, J. W. (Box 19)
    - Myers, Hiram (Box 19)
    - Neuhoff, Hector (Box 19)
    - Orr, D. L. (Box 19)
    - Parsons, L. B. (Box 19)
    - Pendleton, E. W. (Box 19)
    - Phelps, J. W. (Box 19)
    - Reed, Homer (Box 19)
    - Rexford, D. C. (Box 19)
    - Rosevelt, John B. (Box 19)
    - Schreeb, E. W. (Box 19)
    - Seeley, F. L. (Box 19)
    - Smith, Barton (Box 19)
    - Snyder, M. B. (Box 19)
    - Spalding, E. M. (Box 19)
    - Swartz, Hiram Bruell (Box 19)
    - Tabor, F. H. (Box 19)
    - Temple, W. J. (Box 19)
    - Tinkham, Russell F. (Box 19)
    - Tschirgi, Matthew (Box 19)
    - Turner, Chas K. (Box 19)
    - Underwood, W. T. (Box 19)
    - Updike, Herbert D. (Box 19)
    - Van Vranken, H. H. (Box 19)
    - Voorheis, Geo. P. (Box 19)
    - Williams, Geo. P. (Box 19)
    - Wilson, Theo. B. (Box 19)
    - Woodhams, R. (Box 19)
    - Woods, J. A. (Box 19)
    - Woodward, R. S. (Box 19)
    - Worthington, Chas C. (Box 19)
- 1872 Class Albumn
  - Miscellaneous
    - Class of 72 (Box 20)
      [1.]
    - Class Banner (Box 20)
    - Observatory (Box 20)
    - Medical Building (Box 20)
    - Law Building (Box 20)
    - Interior of Library (Box 20)
    - University Hall (Box 20)
    - View of the Campus (Box 20)
    - Adams, C. K. (Box 20)
    - Allyn, George W. (Box 20)
    - Andrews, Frank D. (Box 20)
    - Ayer, Edwin J. (Box 20)
    - Barber, Austin (Box 20)
    - Barker, Charles O. (Box 20)
    - Barton Smith (Box 20)
    - Bennett, Chas G. (Box 20)
    - Bethea, Solomon H. (Box 20)
    - Brooks, Walter A. (Box 20)
    - Brown, Archer H. (Box 20)
    - Bunker, Robert E. (Box 20)
    - Burgett, J. M. H. (Box 20)
    - Burton, H. F. (Box 20)
    - Christie, James (Box 20)
    - Chute, Horatio N. (Box 20)
    - Clark, Charlemagne (Box 20)
    - Cochran, Geo. E. (Box 20)
    - Colt, Jr., George (Box 20)
    - Cooley, Edgar A. (Box 20)
    - D'Ooge, Martin L. (Box 20)
    - Dey, Hamilton (Box 20)
    - Dixon, George (Box 20)
    - Donovan, Cornelius (Box 20)
    - Douglass, Silas H. (Box 20)
    - Dutton, J. Fred (Box 20)
    - Flagg, John H. (Box 20)
    - Ford, Corydon L. (Box 20)
    - Foster, Riley (Box 20)
    - Frieze, H. S. (Box 20)
    - Geddes, Fred L. (Box 20)
    - Haskell, W. S. (Box 20)
    - Herdman, Will J. (Box 20)
    - Hiestand, Henry (Box 20)
    - Hill, Eben L. (Box 20)
    - Hilligass, Jeremiah (Box 20)
    - Hinman, William H. (Box 20)
    - Hosmer, W. A. (Box 20)
    - Houseman, C. L. (Box 20)
    - Hurd, George F. (Box 20)
    - Iddings, Louis M. (Box 20)
    - Jennings, Louis H. (Box 20)
    - Jones, Clark (Box 20)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 20)
    - Jones, Joseph C. (Box 20)
    - Keeler, Hiram M. (Box 20)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jas H. (Box 20)
    - Klotz, Otto J. (Box 20)
    - Leigh, W. R. (Box 20)
    - Lothrop, Charles B. (Box 20)
    - Lyons, Herbert H. (Box 20)
    - Maguire, J. H. (Box 20)
    - Mapel, John J. (Box 20)
    - McCandle, O. D. (Box 20)
    - McGrath, Joseph (Box 20)
    - McKee, William H. (Box 20)
    - McLean, Lester (Box 20)
    - Merriman, Geo. B. (Box 20)
    - Milner, Samuel G. (Box 20)
    - Mitchell, John A. (Box 20)
    - Moffat, Addison (Box 20)
    - Morris, Geo. S. (Box 20)
    - Morrow, Jackson (Box 20)
    - Morton, John W. (Box 20)
    - Myers, Hiram (Box 20)
    - Neuhoff, Hector (Box 20)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 20)
    - Orr, David L. (Box 20)
    - Parsons, Lewis B. (Box 20)
    - Pendleton, E. W. (Box 20)
    - Phelps, John W. (Box 20)
    - Reed, Homer (Box 20)
    - Rexford, Dwight C. (Box 20)
    - Rosevelt, John B. (Box 20)
    - Schreeb, E. W. (Box 20)
    - Seeley, Frank L. (Box 20)
    - Snyder, M. B. (Box 20)
    - Spaulding, Edmund M. (Box 20)
    - Swartz, Hiram B. (Box 20)
    - Tabor, F. H. (Box 20)
    - Temple, Marvin F. (Box 20)
    - Tinkham, Russell F. (Box 20)
    - Tschirgi, Matthew (Box 20)
    - Turner, Chas K. (Box 20)
    - Tyler, Moses C. (Box 20)
    - Underwood, William T. (Box 20)
    - Updike, Herbert D. (Box 20)
    - Van Vranken, H. H. (Box 20)
    - Voorheis, Geo. P. (Box 20)
    - Walter, Edward L. (Box 20)
    - Williams, Geo. P. (Box 20)
    - Wilson, Theo. B. (Box 20)
    - Winchell, Alex (Box 20)
    - Wood, Devolson (Box 20)
    - Woodhams, Roland (Box 20)
    - Woods, James A. (Box 20)
    - Woodward, Robert S. (Box 20)
    - Worthington, Chas C. (Box 20)
- 1872 Class Album (Literary and Engineering)
  (Album of Cornelius Donovan)
  - Faculty
    - Angell, James B., President (Box 21)
    - Douglas, S.H. (Box 21)
    - Ex. President Haven (Box 21)
    - Ex. President Tappan (Box 21)
    - Williams, George.P. (Box 21)
    - Prof. Wood (Box 21)
  - Students
    - Frank D. Andrus, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Edwin J. Ayer, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Charles O. Baker, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Austin Barber, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Charles.G. Bennett, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Solomon H. Bethea, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Walter A. Brooks, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Archer H. Brown, B.W. (Box 21)
    - Robert E. Bunker, B.A. (Box 21)
    - John M. Burgett, PhB. (Box 21)
    - Henry F. Burton (Box 21)
    - James Christie, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Horatio H. Chute, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Charlemagne Clark, B.A. (Box 21)
    - George E. Cochran, B.A. (Box 21)
    - George E. Colt, Jr., B.A. (Box 21)
    - E.A. Cooley, B.A. (Box 21)
    - H. Dey, Ph.B. (Box 21)
    - Cornelius Donovan, C.E. (Box 21)
    - John F. Dutton, B.A. (Box 21)
    - John H. Flagg, C.E. (Box 21)
    - Riley Foster, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Fred L. Geddes, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Henry S. Haskell,. (Box 21)
    - Will J. Herdman, Ph.B. (Box 21)
    - Henry Hiestand, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Eben L. Hill, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Jeremiah Hillegass, B.A. (Box 21)
    - William H. Hinman (Box 21)
    - Warren A. Hosmer, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Charles L. Houseman, Ph.B. (Box 21)
    - George F. Hurd, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Louis M. Iddings, PhB. (Box 21)
    - Louis H. Jennings, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Clark Jones, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Joseph C. Jones, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Hiram M. Keeler, B.A. (Box 21)
    - James H. Kirkpatrick, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Otto J. Klotz, C.E. (Box 21)
    - William R. Leigh, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Charles B. Lothrop, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Herbert H. Lyons, B.A. (Box 21)
    - James H Maguire, B.A. (Box 21)
    - John J. Mapel, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Joseph. McGrath, B.A. (Box 21)
    - William H. McKee, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Lester McLean, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Samuel G. Milner, B.A. (Box 21)
    - John A. Mitchell, C.E. (Box 21)
    - Addison Moffat, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Jackson Morrow, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Hiram Myers (Box 21)
    - John W. Morton, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Hector Neuhoff, B.A. (Box 21)
    - David L. Orr (Box 21)
    - Edward W. Pendleton, B.A. (Box 21)
    - John W. Phelps, Ph.B. (Box 21)
    - Lewis Parsons (Box 21)
    - Homer Reed, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Dwight C. Rexford, B.A. (Box 21)
    - John B. Rosevelt, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Ernest W. Schreeb, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Frank T. Seeley, B.S. (Box 21)
    - Barton Smith, B.S. (Box 21)
      71]
    - Monroe B. Snyder, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Edmund M. Spaulding, C.E. (Box 21)
    - Hiram B. Swartz, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Frank H. Tabor, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Marvin F. Temple, C.E. (Box 21)
    - Russell F. Tinkham, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Matthew Tschirgi, C.E. (Box 21)
    - Charles K. Turner, B.A. (Box 21)
    - William T. Underwood, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Herbert D. Updike, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Howard Van Vranken,B.A. (Box 21)
    - George P. Voorheis, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Theodore B. Wilson, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Roland Woodhams, B.A. (Box 21)
    - James A. Woods, B.A. (Box 21)
    - Robert S. Woodward, C.E. (Box 21)
    - Charles C. Worthington, B.S. (Box 21)
- 1872 Class Album (Literary and Engineering)
  (Album of Otto Klotz)
  - Professors
    - Tappan, Henry (Box 22)
    - Angell, James B. (Box 22)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 22)
    - Morris, G. S. (Box 22)
    - DePont, Paul R. (Box 22)
    - Watson, J. (Box 22)
    - Composite photo of faculty, with Haven, Ford, Sager, Palmer, and Douglas identified (Box 22)
    - Williams, G. P. (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Class Banner (Box 22)
    - Group photo, Class of '72 (Box 22)
    - Engineers of '72 (Box 22)
  - Students
    - Andrus, Frank D. (Box 22)
    - Ayer, Edwin, J. (Box 22)
    - Baker, Chas O. (Box 22)
    - Barber, Austin (Box 22)
    - Bethea, Solomon Alex (Box 22)
    - Brooks, Walter A. (Box 22)
    - Brown, J. A. H. (Box 22)
    - Bunker, Robb Emmet (Box 22)
    - Burgett, J. M. H. (Box 22)
    - Burnett, Chas G. (Box 22)
    - Burton, Henry F. (Box 22)
    - Christie, J. (Box 22)
    - Chute, H. H. (Box 22)
    - Clark, Charlemagne (Box 22)
    - Cochran, G. E. (Box 22)
    - Colt, Jr., George (Box 22)
    - Cooley, E. A. (Box 22)
    - Dey, Hamilton (Box 22)
    - Dickson, Geo. (Box 22)
    - Donovan, C. (Box 22)
    - Dutton, J. Fred (Box 22)
    - Flagg, John H. (Box 22)
    - Foster, Riley (Box 22)
    - Geddes, F. L. (Box 22)
    - H. M. Keeler (Box 22)
    - Haskell, W. S. (Box 22)
    - Herdman, Will (Box 22)
    - Hiestand, Henry (Box 22)
    - Hill, E. L. (Box 22)
    - Hillegass, Jerry (Box 22)
    - Hinman, W. H. (Box 22)
    - Hosmer, W. A. (Box 22)
    - Houseman, C. L. (Box 22)
    - Hurd, G. D. (Box 22)
    - Iddlings, Louis M. (Box 22)
    - James, C. (Box 22)
    - James, J. C. (Box 22)
    - Jennings, L. H. (Box 22)
    - Kirkpatrick, J. V. (Box 22)
    - Klotz, O. J. (Box 22)
    - Leigh, W. R. (Box 22)
    - Lothrop, Charles B. (Box 22)
    - Lyons, H. H. (Box 22)
    - Maguire, J. H. (Box 22)
    - Mapel, J. J. (Box 22)
    - McGrath, J. M. (Box 22)
    - McKee, William H. (Box 22)
    - McLean, L. (Box 22)
    - Milner, S. G. (Box 22)
    - Mitchell, John A. (Box 22)
    - Moffat, A. (Box 22)
    - Morrow, Jackson (Box 22)
    - Morton, J. W. (Box 22)
    - Myers, Hiram (Box 22)
    - Neuhoff, Hector (Box 22)
    - Orr, D. L. (Box 22)
    - Parsons, L. B. (Box 22)
    - Pendleton, E. W. (Box 22)
    - Phelps, J. W. (Box 22)
    - Reed, Homer (Box 22)
    - Rexford, D. C. (Box 22)
    - Rosevelt, John B. (Box 22)
    - Schreeb, E. W. (Box 22)
    - Seeley, J. J. (Box 22)
    - Smith, Barton (Box 22)
    - Snyder, M. B. (Box 22)
    - Spalding, E. M. (Box 22)
    - Swartz, H. B. (Box 22)
    - Tabor, F. H. (Box 22)
    - Temple, M. F. (Box 22)
    - Tinkham, Russell F. (Box 22)
    - Tschirgi, Matthew (Box 22)
    - Turner, C. K. (Box 22)
    - Underwood, W. (Box 22)
    - Updike, Herbert D. (Box 22)
    - VanVranken, H. H. (Box 22)
    - Voorheis, G. P. (Box 22)
    - Wilson, Theo B. (Box 22)
    - Woodhams, R. (Box 22)
    - Woods, J. A. (Box 22)
    - Woodward, R. S. (Box 22)
    - Worthington, Chas. C. (Box 22)
- 1873 Class Album (Literary)
  (Album of Clark H. Gleason)
  - Graduates
    - Benson, William (Box 23)
    - Bishop, Arthur G. (Box 23)
    - Bliss, Frank E. (Box 23)
    - Brush, Alfred Erskine (Box 23)
    - Brush, Eliot Hunt (Box 23)
    - Burritt, Dwight N. (Box 23)
    - Buzzell, Wilbur (Box 23)
    - Carrier, William M. (Box 23)
    - Clarke, William F. (Box 23)
    - Cocker, Henry Reed (Box 23)
    - Dane, Charles H. (Box 23)
    - Darling, John Henry (Box 23)
    - Davis, Herbert E. (Box 23)
    - Decker, Wilhelmus (Box 23)
    - Douglas, Samuel T. (Box 23)
    - Eastman, Sidney C. (Box 23)
    - Elliott, Henry W. (Box 23)
    - Emery, Thomas (Box 23)
    - Fairbank, Henry W. (Box 23)
    - Farr, Frank Ward (Box 23)
    - Ferdon, Edwin J. (Box 23)
    - Fox, William Henry (Box 23)
    - Galloway, Elias D. (Box 23)
    - Gass, Herschel R. (Box 23)
    - Gass, Marshall T. (Box 23)
    - Gelston, Henry W. (Box 23)
    - Gleason, Clark H. (Box 23)
    - Goffe, James R. (Box 23)
    - Granger, William W. (Box 23)
    - Gross, Robert S. (Box 23)
    - Guernsey, Frank W. (Box 23)
    - Hapgood, Mary F. (Box 23)
    - Harrison, Richard D. (Box 23)